

JOSEPH OLUMUYIWA

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

I have over 10 years of experience in related job positions. I started working as a Operation Agent in an IT company gradually moving to a Manager. I am a team player. I am outgoing, dedicated, and openminded. I get across to people and adjust to changes with ease. I believe that a person should work on developing their professional skills and learning new things all the time.

EXPERTISE

CSS Management

HTML Skills

Critical Thinking JavaScript

Leadership ReactJS

EDUCATION

2022 - 2023

Digital Career Institute gGmbH

Certificate in Fullstack Web Development

2013(Jan-Aug)

Redeemed International Leadership Academy

Diploma in Leadership and Theology

1995 - 2002

Obafemi Awolowo University

Bachelor of Arts - French

LANGUAGE

CERTIFICATE

Fullstack Web Development

DCI Digital Career Institute

German Language

English

German

French

Yoruba

2023

2021

Level B2

WORK EXPERIENCE

2017 - Present

Accountant

Kingscourt Leipzig e.V.

- 1. Bookeeping
- 2. End of year review
- 3. Provide periodic reports of outstanding payments

2015 - 2016

2012 - 2014

Pastor

Kingscourt Leipzig e.V.

Assist with activities which includes

- 1. Teaching Sunday School Classes
- 2. Attend weekdays meeting, the regular church management meeting
- 3. Organized the Workers Training

CONTACT

+49 173 5362106

Gersterstr., 15 04279 Leipzig Germany

Liaison Manager/Administrator City of David Missions

Responsible to

- 1. Provide monthly financial report, and other
- 2. Prepare and submit budget for approval
- 3. Monitor budget, and seek approval for funds transfer
- 4. Prepare presentations document for board meetings
- 5. Send out meeting notices, agenda, and meeting materials for Board meetings
- 6. Draft announcements and circulate in newsletters, bulletins.

joe.olumuyiwa@gmail.com